# ROBERTO ESCOBAR

ESCOBAR.ROBERTO@OUTLOOK.COM | C: 415-684-3266 | San Francisco, CA 94110

### Summary

Reliable and hardworking Bartender, familiar with working alone or with team to serve a multitude of customers per shift. Experienced in supporting servers, delivering food and bussing tables. Good interpersonal and multitasking skills in fast-paced environments.

#### Skills

- English
- Spanish
- Streamline
- Detail oriented
- Communicator

- Inventory
- Team player
- High-volume dining
- Problem solving
- Courteous

## **Experience**

11/2016 - 08/2017

**Lead Server** 

- RED DOG RESTAURANT Educated guests on daily specials and menu offerings such as appetizers, entrees and desserts.
- & BAR SAN FRANCISCO, Assisted management with training new team members, bussers, food runners, bartenders.

**CALIFORNIA** 

Worked closely with team members and management to ensure that every guest were well attended to.

03/2016 - 03/2018

Pompeis Grotto

San Francisco, CA

- **Bartender**
- Worked with management to plan and implement special events to boost customer numbers and profits.
- Promoted customer safety by maintaining current list of available ride services for inebriated customers.
- Checked identification of customers to verify age requirements needed for purchase of alcohol.

08/2017 - 08/2018

San Francisco, CA

- Scoma's Restaurant Inc. Kept detailed inventories of bar supplies and kept work areas stocked to maintain workflow efficiently.
  - Restocked condiments and drink station supplies to maintain customer satisfaction.
  - Made product recommendations to customers based on preference, food pairings and special promotions.

02/2017 - 12/2019

**Bartender** 

The Pub At Ghirardelli Square

- Supported servers by preparing specialty drinks for patrons in all areas of establishment.
- Promoted products to customers to enhance bill totals with high-profit items.
- San Francisco, CA
- Ordered and maintained inventory of bar products, including alcohol, soft drinks and supplies to drive high volume of sales.

# **Education and Training**

2009

**Diploma** 

San Francisco, CA

Galileo High School